[{"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I don't think he did that badly.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Why did he do so badly?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I think that we were all a little taken aback by Mitt Romney's performance and he --Mitt Romney had a great performance.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Sorry?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Is he right when he says that?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Now if you do the math on that --", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Do you believe him?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "-- there aren't enough loopholes and deductions that equal $5 trillion.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Do you believe him?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I don't think he's being honest about his tax cut.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "So he is lying, you think?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, we shall find out, no doubt.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "So which is it?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Stephanie Cutter wants an answer out of your guys.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Hey, Piers, how are you?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I would say that listening to Stephanie's interview, I mean, it's just symptomatic of what's been going on with the Obama campaign since last week's debate.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Have you any idea?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Look, look, Piers, you know, President Obama has talked about reducing the corporate tax rate.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "But do we anticipate from the Romney camp, from Mitt Romney himself, in the next 28 days, that we will get the devil of the detail on this?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "What are you anticipating?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, you know, people are going to have their own opinion, and that's the point.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "How have you dealt with the fallout from all this?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I would say because of the state of the country and I want the next four years to be different.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Why have you decided to change to Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "You know, in the -- I really don't understand the fury.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What do you think has been the predominant factor in the fury?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Were you saddened?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I mean, really disgusting.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Just come on.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "You think it's stupid?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Have you heard from Mitt Romney at all?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes, he did.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Paul Ryan rang you today?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "He said thank you so much for your support and that I was brave and that they support me.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "What did he say?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "No, they haven't.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Any of the Obama campaign been on?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I think it tells me that our state -- the state of our country is that we are not united.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "What does it say to you about the state of the political discourse and debate in America that one innocuous tweet from you, purely because you're an actress and the color of your skin, sparked this kind of mayhem?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "He's an Obama -- yes, he's an Obama man and that's fine.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "So he's an Obama man?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, listen, I think that it's unfortunate that anybody can make up their mind and vote however they want.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I think maybe there's some bit of both.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Do you think it was mainly because she was a black actress or because she was an actress and actually in Hollywood there aren't many actresses who say vote Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I think there are lots of blacks supporting Romney.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "So why the fury?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, you can't say both things.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Charles Blow?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, again, you know, I think what we just heard from Charles, who is a prominent liberal, is exactly part of I think this problem, is that we whittle around the fact that when liberals are intolerant, we can't say it for some reason.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Rick, what do you make of what happened to him, to Jack Welch?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "What I'm saying, Charles, is that you can't just say that intolerance exists.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Are you seriously saying that I didn't say that?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I think that on the stump you get a much more passionate Barack Obama.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "People are like we would vote for Clinton but why isn't the president doing this?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Well, it's the big white elephant in the room we can't avoid.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "How are you handling it?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "It's years.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "This is years old, right?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "No, I had no idea there was a camera set up.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "You didn't know you had been videotaped?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "At this point, no.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you any nearer to knowing who betrayed you?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "It was all about change.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I think we're in trouble.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "What do you make of America right now?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "No, that's what's so funny, is, you know, I really don't go to bars.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "When you go into bars and things, do people come up and try it on?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "It's been a rough ride.", "docId": "121009pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "In terms of injuries you sustained, what physical shape are you in?", "qSentId": 649}]